Do you often feel stressed?
你经常感到“压力山大”吗？
Does the pace of life make you feel like you're continually on the go or at the end of your rope?
快节奏的生活是否让你觉得自己一直在奔波忙碌，或是陷入了绝望的境地？
Are you often so wiped out by work that you struggle to switch off?
你是否常常被工作累得筋疲力尽，连放松下来都很难？
And are you a member of the millennial generation, who, according to the Pew Research Center, were born between 1981 and 1996?
另外，你是否属于千禧一代？根据皮尤研究中心的定义，千禧一代指的是1981年至1996年间出生的人。
If your answer to these questions is 'yes', maybe you suffer from 'millennial burnout'.
如果这些问题你的答案都是“是”，那你或许正遭受“千禧一代倦怠症”的困扰。
Millennial burnout is a term first popularised by BuzzFeed writer Anne Helen Petersen.
“千禧一代倦怠症”这个说法，最初是由美国聚合新闻网站的撰稿人安妮·海伦·彼得森推广开来的。
Unlike 'regular' burnout, which leaves sufferers feeling physically and emotionally frazzled, run into the ground and overwhelmed, millennial burnout also adds, among other things, 'errand paralysis'.
普通倦怠症会让患者身心俱疲、心力交瘁、不堪重负，而千禧一代倦怠症除此之外，还会引发一种“琐事瘫痪症”。
This is when minor tasks, such as cleaning the car, or sending a parcel in the mail, feel impossible.
具体表现为，就连洗车、去邮局寄包裹这类小事，都会让人觉得难以完成。
"It's not as if I were slacking in the rest of my life," she wrote. "But when it came to the stuff that wouldn't make my job easier or my work better, I avoided it."
她在文中写道：“我不会在生活其他方面偷懒，但遇到那些没法让我的工作更轻松、表现更出色的事情时，我就会刻意回避。”
So it doesn't get done, which leads to a backlog of tasks and feelings of shame.
这些事就此被搁置，久而久之就会堆积成山，进而让人产生愧疚感。
In the UK, 74% of us feel so stressed that we are coming apart at the seams, mentalhealth.org reports.
心理健康组织的报告显示，在英国，有74%的人因为压力过大而濒临崩溃。
So why are millennials tearing their hair out?
那么，为什么千禧一代会如此焦虑抓狂呢？
Millennials feel their problems are 'exacerbated by social media, because of the constant pressure to be living up to your best life,' British psychotherapist Beverly Hills told the BBC.
英国心理治疗师贝弗莉·希尔斯在接受英国广播公司采访时表示，千禧一代的问题“因社交媒体而加剧，因为他们时刻都承受着要活出完美人生的压力”。
This pressure is made worse when the definition of 'success' seems to have changed.
而“成功”的定义似乎也发生了改变，这让他们的压力雪上加霜。
It used to be about earning money, but now it's things like being passionate about work, being super-healthy, holidaying and having amazing experiences, etc.
过去，成功的标准是赚钱，但如今，成功被定义为热爱工作、拥有极佳的健康状态、频繁度假以及拥有丰富多彩的人生体验等。
That's a lot to have on your plate and the 'failure' to cope leaves many feeling guilty, ashamed and at their wits' end.
要兼顾这么多事情实属不易，一旦无法做到，很多人就会陷入愧疚、羞耻与手足无措的情绪中。
However, the concept of millennial burnout has not gone unchallenged.
不过，“千禧一代倦怠症”这个概念也并非毫无争议。
Many have said that it's merely a form of entitled laziness or the result of poor choices – for example, trying to do too much.
很多人认为，这不过是一种恃宠而骄的懒惰，或是不当选择的后果，比如想要做太多事情。
After all, as psychoanalyst Josh Cohen writes for NBC, this isn't the first generation to suffer from overwork and exhaustion, nor is it the first to have to adapt to new forms of technology and culture.
毕竟，正如精神分析师乔希·科恩在为美国全国广播公司撰稿时所写的那样，这并非第一代遭受过度劳累和疲惫之苦的人，也不是第一代必须去适应新技术、新文化的群体。
Could the answer simply be that millennial ambition reaches too far?
答案可能非常简单——千禧一代想要的太多了？